<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Anova / Factorial Anova on Lionel Tay</title>
    <link>https://lioneltayyd.github.io/site/data_statistical_analysis/anova_or_factorial_anova/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Anova / Factorial Anova on Lionel Tay</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 22:36:38 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://lioneltayyd.github.io/site/data_statistical_analysis/anova_or_factorial_anova/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Investigate The Cold Storage Milk Quality Maintainance</title>
      <link>https://lioneltayyd.github.io/site/data_statistical_analysis/anova_or_factorial_anova/investigate_the_cold_storage_milk_quality_maintainance/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 22:36:38 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lioneltayyd.github.io/site/data_statistical_analysis/anova_or_factorial_anova/investigate_the_cold_storage_milk_quality_maintainance/</guid>
      <description>Investigate The Cold Storage Milk Quality Maintainance. Project purpose. Cold Storage started its operations in Jan 2016. They are in the business of storing Pasteurized Fresh Whole or Skimmed Milk, Sweet Cream, Flavoured Milk Drinks. To ensure that there is no change of texture, body appearance, separation of fats the optimal temperature to be maintained is between 2—4°C.
In the first year of business, they outsourced the plant maintenance work to a professional company with stiff penalty clauses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Researching The Effect Of Disability On Device Preference</title>
      <link>https://lioneltayyd.github.io/site/data_statistical_analysis/anova_or_factorial_anova/researching_the_effect_of_disability_on_device_preference/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 22:36:38 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lioneltayyd.github.io/site/data_statistical_analysis/anova_or_factorial_anova/researching_the_effect_of_disability_on_device_preference/</guid>
      <description>Researching The Effect Of Disability On Device Preference. Project purpose. The user research team conducted an experiment design to find out whether disability has an effect on the device preference. There are two groups of users, one with disability and another without. They were asked to use two different devices, touchpads and trackballs as computer input devices, and pick their preference. Now that the data is collected, the objective is to conduct a statistical testing to see whether disability has a signifcant effect on device preference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Researching The User Preference On Note-taking Apps</title>
      <link>https://lioneltayyd.github.io/site/data_statistical_analysis/anova_or_factorial_anova/researching_the_user_preference_on_note_taking_apps/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 22:36:38 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lioneltayyd.github.io/site/data_statistical_analysis/anova_or_factorial_anova/researching_the_user_preference_on_note_taking_apps/</guid>
      <description>Researching The User Preference On Note-taking Apps. Project purpose. The user research team conducted an experiment design to find out whether users use built-in-app or third-party-app more often for note-taking. There are 20 users. Each user were asked to use both built-in-app and third-party-app on either iPhone or Andriod in different order. The users were randomly assigned to specifc order and device. Meaning, some users will use built-in-app first, while others will use third-app-party first, however, each users will use one device only.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>